["Love Mate" shooting set]
You know what?
Everyone's talking
about their photo
Yeah, I know
Shin Yoo-il's always
been a superstar
but Lee Hyesung
truly hit the jackpot
Let's get started!
Hello, Yoo-il…
I'm sorry
I couldn't come with you
due to a shooting
It's okay
I just got here too
What shall we do now?
It's our first day
Uh…
Shall we go
over there first?
Sure, let's go
I'm a little nervous
to meet your friend
Relax
He's just an old friend…
Are you crying?
No, it's because
of onions
Let me take a look
Hyesung
If we kiss now
this episode will be
a big hit, right?
Oh, our guest is here
I'll get it
Nice to meet you
I'm Hyesung's boyfriend
Shin Yoo-il
I'm Yoon Soobin